A Guide to the Papers of Robert Morton Hughes 1767-1959.
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Oversized Materials
  - Certificate of Appointment as Federal Judge for the Eastern District of Virginia January 14, 1874 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment to Board of Visitors of the College of William and Mary 1908 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment to Board of Visitors of the College of William and Mary 1910 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment to Board of Visitors of the College of William and Mary 1914 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment to Board of Examiners of Applicants for Admission to the Bar 1910 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment to Board of Examiners of Applicants for Admission to the Bar 1912 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment to Board of Examiners of Applicants for Admission to the Bar 1917 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment to the Commission to Suggest Amendments to the Virginia Constitution 1926 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment as Virginia Delegate at Institute of Public Affairs Meeting August 15-18, 1928 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment to the State Board of Education 1930 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment to the State Board of Education 1933 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Appointment as Virginia Delegate to Conference of American Library Association June 22-27, 1931 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of Latin 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of Greek 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of Junior and Intermediate Mathematics 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of Literature and Rhetoric 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of General Chemistry 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of German Language and Literature 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of French Language and Literature 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of History, Literature and Rhetoric 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of Moral Philosophy 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of Pure Mathematics 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Certificate of Graduation from the University of Virginia School of Natural Philosophy 1877 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Diploma Conferring the Degree of Bachelor of Arts on Robert M. Hughes by the College of William and Mary 1873 (Box Oversize Box 1)
  - Ledger Book Listing Holdings in Robert M. Hughes' Personal Library (Box Oversize Box 2)
  - Ledger Book Listing Holdings in Law Library of Sharp and Hughes 1901 (Box Oversize Box 2)
  - Scrapbook Featuring Newspaper Clippings on Roosevelt and the Supreme Court 1935-1937 (Box Oversize Box 2)
  - Binder Containing Positive Photocopy of Mrs. Letitia Floyd's Letter to Benjamin Rush Floyd February 22, 1843 (Box Oversize Box 2)
  - Binder Containing Negative Photocopy of Mrs. Letitia Floyd's Letter to Benjamin Rush Floyd February 22, 1843 (Box Oversize Box 2)
  - Scrapbook entitled "Personal and Civil War/Spanish-American War 1898" 1898 (Box Oversized Box 3)
    Contains: Magazine Articles, Poems, Newspaper Clippings, Governor John Garland Pollard's Proclamation of the New Seal of the Commonwealth of Virginia, Invitation and photographs of the unveiling of the bust of General Johnston, etc.
  - Scrapbook entitled "Personal and Civil War" (Box Oversized Box 4)
    Contains: Magazine Articles, Poems, Newspaper Clippings, genealogical information on the Johnston Family, typed copies of correspondence relating to the duel of Robert W. Hughes and William Cameron, typed autobiographical sketch of John Warfield Johnston, biographical sketch of Judge Peter Johnston, photographs of the Joseph E. Johnston Monument in Dalton, Georgia, other photographs, lithographs and sketches.